爸爸，发生了什么？
Dad, what's happening?
尼克，听我说
Nick, listen to me,
就像这个星球上只剩咱俩一样那么认真
like we're the last 2 people on the planet.
好吗？尼克
Okay? Nick,
如果有一天 有个女孩儿给你一朵花
Some day a girl is gonna give you a flower.
记住了吗？一朵花
You got that? A flower.
你一定要帮她
And you have to help her.
帮她就是救了所有人
You help her and you help us all.
好吗？
Okay?
我知道现在对你说这些没有意义
I know it doesn't make any sense right now,
可我相信那个告诉我这件事的女人
but I believe the woman who told me that.
你相信我吗？
You think you could believe me?
我爱你
I love you.
我一直都说你是个与众不同的孩子，尼克
I always said you were special, Nick.
你要证明我是对的
Turns out I was right.
组织的人来了，尼克，快跑
Division's here. Nick. Just keep moving.
什么都别想否则任何一个先知都会追踪到你
And don't make any decisions that any watcher can track.
我本来还想能够和他谈谈的
I just wanted to have a conversation.
可惜了
What a waste.
把他的尸体带回实验室
Bring his body to the lab.
世界上有一种具有特异功能的人
There are special people in this world.
这种特异功能并非后天培养形成的
We don't ask to be special.
而是与生俱来
We're just born this way.
我们每天与你在街头擦肩而过
We pass you on the streets every day,
以超乎你想象的频率
unnoticed by most.
【 异能 】
事情始于1945年
It started in 1945.
当时纳粹正在进行一项异能战争的研发试验
The Nazis were conducting experiments in psychic warfare...
目的是要把具备特殊能力的人 变为战争机器
trying to turn those with psychic abilities into soldiers.
我们中很多人因此死亡
Lots of us died.
战争结束后
The war ended,
试验却并未停止
but the experiments never stopped.
世界上的某些政府
Other governments around the world
创立了名为“组织”的秘密机构
set up what they called "Divisions"...
试图实现纳粹们没能实现的愿望
trying to do what the Nazis couldn't,
将我们变成杀人机器
to turn us into weapons.
组织的爪牙们像狩猎动物那样 受训四处追踪我们
Division's agents are trained to track and hunt us down like animals...
将我们从家人和朋友身边带走
take us away from our families and friends.
丢失儿童的现象遍布全球
There are children stuffed away all over the world.
他们检测我们 并依据我们的能力将我们归类
They test us and categorize us.
我则被他们称为“先知”
I'm what they call a "watcher".
我们能够预知未来
We can see the future,
即便这有时并不像听起来这么容易
even if that's not always as simple as it sounds.
客机坠毁 无一人生还
The jumbo jet crashed. There are no reports of survivors.
还有些人被称为“移物人”
Others are called "movers",
是种对“隔空移物”能力的简单说法
just an easy way of saying "telekinetic".
“支配者”能够用他们的意识支配你的大脑
"Pushers" put thoughts in your head
让你把所有的谎言视为真相
and make whatever lie they come up with the truth.
他们已经开始控制我的意识了
They'd already begun to control my mind...
“嗅迹者”“转换者”“影子人”
"Sniffs", "shifters", "shadows",
“吸血鬼”，等等等等
"bleeders", it goes on and on.
在组织看来 我们不过是实验室里的白鼠
In Division's eyes, we're all just lab rats.
只是有一个问题，我们相继死亡
Only one problem: we keep dying.
证据表明这个孩子被喂养一种 含有放射性碘的牛奶
The evidence shows that the kids were given milk with radioactive iodine.
还没有人能够在这种试图被用来提升 我们能力的药物试验中侥幸活下来
No one has ever survived the drug meant to boost our powers.
我叫卡西・霍尔姆斯
My name is Cassie Holmes.
组织带走了我妈妈
Division took my mom from me.
此刻我所遇见的未来并不乐观
Right now the future I see doesn't look so great.
好在，未来在不停的变化着
The good news is the future is always changing...
从质变引发量变
in the largest of ways by the smallest of things.
他们已经取得了太多胜利
They've been winning a lot of battles.
现在，该轮到我们反击了
Now it's our turn to win the war.
今天
" PRESENT DAY "
组织实验室
" DIVISION LAB "
她居然活下来了
She survived the injection.
她是咱们的零号病人 马上集合所有的嗅迹者给我追
She's our patient zero. Bring me every sniffer we have.
可她步行，跑不远的
But she's on foot. She can't get far.
她能从任何一个被她注视的人那儿得到帮助
She'll get help from anyone she can lay her eyes on.
要不择手段把她和那个注射器带回来！
Do whatever is necessary to get her and that syringe back!
马上行动！
Now!!
两天后
" 2 DAYS FROM NOW "
- 早安     - 早安
- Good morning.      - Good morning.
你的 你的 你好彩啊
You-- You are lucky.
你还来，你已经输了五千块了
You still want to play? You've lost 5 grand now...
陈的那笔借款你也还没还
Chan said you still haven't paid him off your debt, huh?
他说谎
He lied...
他说谎？那也就是说我也说谎了？
He lied? Are you suggesting I'm lying?
你尚欠了十五万没还
You already got 15 grand of debts, do the math.
你到底还赌不赌？
You want to bet or not?
这么拽？好啊！
How arrogant-- Okay!
如果他再输，就给我揍他
If he loses again, we gonna fix him up with punches.
快点啦！
Hurry up!
如果你再输，我就揍扁你
If you lose, we gonna have to beat you up this time.
当心留神
Watch your step.
现在你欠我们六千块了，尼克！
You still owe me 5 grand!
最近怎么样，尼克？
What do you say, Nick?
你们是谁？
Who are you?
- 我们是组织派来的      - 你看起来什么都不知道嘛
- We're with Division.      - Like you didn't know.
- 见鬼去吧      - 别紧张，孩子
- Go to hell.      - Easy, son.
如果我们想要你 你这会儿已经躺在在后备箱里了
If we wanted you, you'd be in the back of a van.
你是打算请我们进去呢 还是让我们动粗？
You gonna let us in or are we gonna have to be rude?
潇洒的移物小子住的地方活像个粪坑
Smart move living in a shithole like this.
这地方可以让你远离尘嚣
One on top of the other. Took you far off the radar.
看来还不够远
Not far enough.
你相信我们就是通过这东西找到你的吗？
Would you believe this is how we found you?
你的旧牙刷 十年前在那家宾馆用过的
From your old toothbrush from that encounter 10 years ago.
上面残留着你的气味
Barely a scent left.
我们曾以为你在东京
Thought you were in Tokyo.
之后去了马来西亚
Then Malaysia.
最终我们从一些建筑物里获悉你在这
Finally we got a few readings on some buildings.
很多异能者都想在香港隐姓埋名，尼克
There's a lot of runaway psychics in Hong Kong trying to disappear. Nick.
都是些没有国籍，没有忠诚
People with no country, no loyalty...
也没有欲望卷入政治纷争的人
No desire to get involved in political bullshit.
除了你，很久没其他人来过这间公寓了，尼克
Nobody but you in this apartment for a long time, Nick.
怎么了？你们是要找我身边某个人吗？
Why? You looking for someone besides me?
一个女孩儿
A girl.
她拿走了属于我们的东西
She has something belonging to us.
好在你认识她
Better than a hunch you know her.
明显不可能
Obviously I don't.
这是为了方便我们能够再找到你
In case we need to get hold of you again.
我还有些擦屁股纸你们可能更喜欢
I've got some old toilet paper you boys might like more.
别费心思想逃跑，尼克
Don't bother running.
无论你到哪儿我们都知道
We know where you are now.
妈的
Shit.
- 喂？      - 嘿，尼克
- Yeah?      - Hey, Nick.
- 你是谁？      - 把门打开，尼克
- Who is this?      - Open up, Nick.
把枪放下
And put your gun down.
把那东西拿开 给你带了东西
Put that thing away. Got you something.
鸡肉放哪儿了？在这儿
Where's the chicken? There it is.
嘿！哇哦！抱歉了
Hey, whoa! Excuse me?
你就是这么招待客人的？
Is this how you treat your guests?
我就是这样招待突然闯入我公寓的陌生人的
This is how I treat random strangers who barge into my apartment.
比如刚才那些组织的嗅迹者？
Like the Division sniffers who were just here?
你到底是谁？
Who are you?
我是卡西
I'm Cassie.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you.
听着，卡西
Listen, Cassie...
我相信你爸妈这会儿正在为你担心 你为什么不…
I'm sure your mom and dad are nervous about you right now, so why don't you...
- 你不了解      - 说的没错
- You don't understand.      - You've got that right.
是关于咱们要找六百万美元的事
This is about us finding 6 million dollars.
这是咱俩
That's us.
这是咱们的钱
And that's our money.
这是我的牙刷
And that's my toothbrush.
你是个先知
You're a watcher.
能不能找个除了鸡肉还有其它食物的地方？
So is there a place we can get something to eat besides chicken?
我买单
I'm buying.
你是不是跟你的发型师打赌打输了？
Lose a bet with your hairdresser?
我喜欢给头发染颜色
I like color.
先说重要的 我知道你是个第二代移物人
First things first. I know you're a second-generation mover.
你们现在的小孩都这么说话吗？
Is that what the kids are calling it these days?
我会把我知道的告诉你的
I'll let you know when I see one.
你还没有真正发挥出你的能力
You don't really use your powers,
我是说你还没有熟练掌握它 只能发挥出来一点儿
which means you haven't practiced and you kind of suck at it.
- 目前为止我说的对吗？      - 继续
- How am I doing so far?      - Go on.
我是个先知
I'm a watcher.
跟你一样，也是第二代的
Second generation, like you.
- 哇哦！那…      - 说起来很复杂
- Wow. That's.      - Complicated.
因为你在讲述着未来的时候 它就已经在发生变化了
Because the future can change just by talking about it.
所以每当我捕获一个场景 我就把它画在本子上
So I see glimpses and I draw in my book.
可我不是很擅长画画
But I'm not really good at it.
我是个蹩脚的画家，可是
I'm kind of a crappy artist, but...
我相信你已经知道了
I'm sure you already knew that.
但我毕竟能知道嗅迹者在你的公寓，对吗？
But I got the sniffs in your apartment, right?
所以我才给你买了新牙刷
That's why I brought you a new toothbrush.
- 老板，我要吃虾      - 好的，没问题
- Chief. I want to eat shrimps.      - Okay.
你会说中文？
You speak Chinese?
广东话 我很惊讶你居然不知道我会广东话
Cantonese. I'm surprised you didn't know that,
作为一个先知
being a watcher.
我有时候会也会出岔子
I get things wrong sometimes.
我知道这种感觉
I know the feeling.
你是不是在为你欠钱的那群流氓烦恼呢？
Are you worried about the thugs you owe money to?
没必要，谢谢
Don't. Thank you.
咱们很快就能把这件事摆平
We'll be able to take care of it in a couple days.
用你所谓的六百万美金？
With your 6 million dollars.
- 钱在哪儿？      - 在路上
- Where's the money?      - It's on its way here.
一个女孩儿带着
With a girl.
别告诉我
Don't tell me.
就是组织的嗅迹者们要找的那个
Same girl Division sniffs are looking for.
你叫卡西，对吗？
It's Cassie, right?
好好享受你的美食
Enjoy your food.
- 就这样？      - 就这样
- That's it?      - That's it.
抱歉了 即便一个12岁的小孩知道我需要个新牙刷
Sorry. Some 12-year old that knew I needed a new toothbrush...
也不足以让我去和组织作对
isn't enough to get me involved with Division.
就算这不是个骗局
Even if it's not a con.
我13岁了，还有人说我看起来像14岁的
I'm 13. And I've been told I look at least 14.
- 好吧      - 还有，这并不是骗局
- Right.      - And this is not a con.
这是想要达到目的使用的一种手段
This is a way for everyone to get something they want.
我以前也用过这招
I've actually used that line before.
好吧，你还是不相信我
Fine. Don't believe me.
- 可是你会帮我的      - 真的吗？
- But you will help me.      - Really?
因为我得到了一个指令
Because I'm getting a message.
告诉我“去找一个人”
It's telling me "find somebody else".
如果我们不找到那个箱子和那女孩儿
If we don't find the case and that girl,
真正糟糕的事就会发生了，尼克
really bad things happen, Nick.
怎么了?发生什么事了?
What? What's wrong?
该死的，他们在这个市场里
Shit. They're here in the market.
谁？
Who?
- 谁？      - 他们就在这儿！快走！
- Who?      - They're in the market! Come on!
- 组织的人？      - 吸血鬼！
- Division?      - Bleeders!
咱们得离开这儿！
We've got to get out of here!
- 咱们会怎么样？      - 我也不知道
- How does this end?      - I have no idea.
那女孩在哪儿？
Where is the girl?
我女儿看到你跟她在一起
My daughter has already seen you with her.
我说吧
Told you.
我今天已经跟三个人说过了 我不认识这个女孩
I've told 3 people already today, I don't know this girl.
愚蠢的小孩 我已经看到你是怎么死的了
Stupid child. I already saw how you die.
那你就该知道不是在这儿 也不是今天
Then you know it's not here and it's not today.
夸张！
Damn.
快跑，快跑！
Go, go!
- 尼克！      - 这边！这边！
- Nick!      - Come here! Come here!
那边的大水缸…去！
The big tanks... Go!
- 快！      - 这边！
- Quick!      - This way!
住口！
Stop!
- 住口！      - 快跑，卡西！
- Stop!      - Run, Cassie!
住口！
Stop!
不是这样
Not like this.
如果咱们杀了他就找不到那个女孩了
lf we kill him we lose the girl.
“4100” “尼克”
“尼克”
我知道你在这儿
I already know you're here.
你一定就是卡西・霍尔姆斯
You must be Cassie Holmes.
- 谁派你来的？      - 你母亲
- Who sent you?      - Your mother.
她在被组织带走的前一周
A week before she was captured by Division,
告诉我今天到鱼市场来
she told me to be at that fish market today.
离他远点儿
Stay away from him.
如果你真想这样
If that's what you want.
那他的照片就一定会挂在这面死者墙上了
Just be sure to add his picture to the Wall of the Dead.
你是个修理者
You're a stitch.
这对一个先知来说应该再明显不过了
That should be obvious to a watcher.
如果你能有你母亲天赋的一小部分…
If you had even a modicum of your mother's talent...
我已经有了不少
I've been dealing with a lot.
几年前，你母亲帮过我一个忙
Years ago your mother did me a favor.
现在似乎就是还她这个人情的时候
Now it would seem I need to pay off my debt.
我听说她们把你母亲关在组织最深处
I hear they've got your mother buried deep inside Division.
给她用药以至于她连勺子都拿不住
Have her so drugged up she can't even hold a spoon.
我打赌他们那样做就是为了逼她说出未来
I bet they suck the future right out of her.
帮她就是救了所有人
You help her and you help us all.
一朵花
A flower
他没事了吧？
Is he okay?
- 你还好吗？      - 是的
- You okay?      - Yeah.
哇哦
Wow.
那女人的手指真神奇
That woman's got magic fingers.
给你的
For you.
这是什么？
What is that?
一朵莲花
It's a lotus.
我听到她说你母亲的事了
I heard what she said about your mother.
是吗？
You did?
组织抓走了她
Division's got her.
他们把她关起来是因为 她是他们见过的最出色的先知
They locked her up because she's the... greatest watcher they've ever seen.
他们怕她
They're afraid of her.
他们更怕控制不了她
And they're afraid they can't control her.
他们也因为这个原因杀了我父亲
They killed my father for the same reason.
我猜这你已经知道了
But I guess you already knew that.
我能看见的是未来，不是过去
I see the future, not the past.
而现在 咱们的未来看起来并不怎么样
And right now our future isn't that great.
你新画的？
That's new?
嗅迹者离开你的公寓后
Now the sniffs from your apartment
就在找这个女孩和箱子
are going to get the girl and the case.
又变了
It's changed.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why...
我做了些事儿，可能犯了个错误
something I did, a mistake I made...
算了，就这样了
Doesn't matter, it just has.
我妈妈曾跟我说起过那个箱子
My mother told me that case...
说那是战胜组织并解救她的关键
is the key to bringing down Division and freeing her.
那箱子里没有钱，是吗？
There's no money in that case, is there?
除非我搞错了
Unless I'm missing something,
否则他们应该还没拿到那个箱子
they don't have the case yet.
它还在某个地方
It's still out there.
如果你母亲真的是位伟大的预言家
If your mother's such a great fortune-teller,
那她是怎么被抓住的？
how did she get caught?
我也正准备去问问她
I'm just going to have to ask her that myself.
我还没说最糟糕的事情呢
I haven't even gotten to the bad part yet.
那是什么？
What is that?
咱们会死
We die.
很好
Great.
嗨，基拉
Hello, Kira.
你得跟我们走一趟
You have a plane to catch.
来吧，你会愿意跟我们走的
Come on. You want to come with us.
天啊，仔细看看这个
Christ. Get a load of that.
她肯定每天用十次 应该储存了很多口红
She must use that 10 times a day. That's a keeper.
你要去的地方不会让你有太多机会用口红的
You're not gonna have a lot of lipstick opportunities where you're going.
你知道我什么意思吗？
You know what I mean?
她又开始了
She's doing it again.
- 快他妈从我脑袋里滚出去！      - 不！不！
- Get the hell out of my head!      - No! No!
- 她想干嘛？      - 她想去洗手间
- What does she want?      - She's got to go to the bathroom.
吐或者干其它的什么
To throw up or something.
如果她出了什么状况 卡维会杀了咱们的
Carver will kill us if anything happens to her.
- 洗手间？      - 这边
- Bathroom?      - This way.
快走
Come on.
黑咖啡，加糖
Coffee, black, with sugar.
好了，进去
Alright. In you go.
你是个好人，麦克长官
You're a good man, Agent Mack.
我敢说你出身一个好家庭
I bet you come from a good family.
他的死一定让你很难过
It must have been hard for you when he died.
谁死了？
Who died?
你弟弟
Your brother.
- 我没有弟弟，亲爱的      - 不，你有
- I don't have a brother, sweetheart.      - No, you do.
我这儿有能让你感觉舒服点的玩意儿
I've got something that will make you feel better.
你非常爱他
And you loved him very much.
可是他被杀了
But he was murdered.
而且你知道是谁干的，不是吗？
And you know who did it, don't you?
可是他被杀了
But he was murdered...
而且你知道是谁干的，不是吗？
And you know who did it, don't you?
你知道是谁干的，不是吗？ 可是他被杀了
You know who did it, don't you? But he was murdered...
你知道是谁干的，他被杀了
You know who did it he was murdered...
真差劲儿
Lame.
如果咱们想做成事儿 你就得好好练练你的能力
We've got to work on your skills if we're going to change anything.
别咬指甲
Don't bite your nails.
那个棒棒糖女人让我感到害怕
The lollipop chick freaks me out.
- 她是个先知      - 跟你一样
- She's a watcher.      - Like you.
对
Yeah.
我知道这个地方，这是…
I know this place. This is...
我知道这里 B俱乐部，老兄，科学博物馆路
I know this place. Club B, boss. Science Museum Road.
谢谢
Thank you.
为什么这个橄榄在杯子外面？
Why is that olive out of the glass?
- 那不是橄榄，是个珠子      - 是个珠子？
- That's not an olive. It's a bead.      - It's a bead?
对，是个珠子，闪着光
Yeah, it's a bead. A shimmery kind of thing...
好吧，可这看起来像个甘椒 如果让我画，我会…
Well, it looks like a pimento. If I was going to draw a bead, I'd...
这是个闪着光的珠子
It's a bead with a shimmer.
这珠子干嘛一定要闪着光？
What does the bead have to do with it?
我不知道这是什么光 但这个珠子肯定和它有关
I don't know what the shiny, shimmery bead has to do with it.
好极了
Great.
咱们别想那么复杂了
Let's keep it simple.
就从这个珠子开始 看看它能把咱们引向何处
We'll start with the bead and see where it takes us.
听着像个计划，可是... 那关于咱俩在哪死的事怎么办？
Sounds like a plan, but... what about the part where we die?
我想起来了我们一起长大
I remember growing up together.
在哪儿上学
Where we went to school.
他是怎么死的
How he died.
那就是说，除了你弟弟 你再也没有…
So except for this brother you never had...
那她还让你想起来了什么吗？
is there anything else she might have put in your head?
我只是随便问问，我可不想因为
I'm only asking because I don't want to be shot in the face...
给你编了个妹妹出来就被你把脸打烂
for screwing some made up sister you don't really have.
我没有妹妹吗？
I don't have a sister?
麦克长官，你被解职了
Agent Mack, you are relieved of duty.
坐上飞机，吃点儿花生回家吧
Get on a plane, eat some peanuts, and go home.
我不会再让她控制了，先生
She won't push me again, sir.
她那是趁我不备才得手的
She just caught me off-guard.
我现在的意识已经不受控制了
The only thoughts in my head are my own.
那你肯拿你的命担保吗？
You're willing to risk your life on that?
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
那就把枪放到自己嘴里 然后开枪
Then put the gun in your mouth and pull the trigger.
不用担心
Don't worry.
你已经检查过了，子弹没上膛
You already checked it. It's not loaded.
把这些珠子交给所有的嗅迹者和先知
Spread these beads to any sniff, any watcher,
还有香港那群该死的外来阅读者
any goddamn expatriate reader in Hong Kong
让他们仔仔细细的查，直到找出基拉
who knows up from down until we find Kira.
那中国政府和和他们的人该怎么处理？
What about the Chinese government and their guys?
事情已经走漏了风声 全国的吸血鬼都在找她
The story is out, bleeders all over the country will be looking for her.
咱们不能让药剂落到他们手里
We can't let them get the drug.
那咱们就给她的脑袋出个价
Then we put a price on her head.
对，就是这儿了
Yeah, this is it.
嘿，你能…我没带钱
Hey, can you... I don't have any...
好的！当然，我有
Yeah! Sure. I got it.
给您，不用找了，谢谢
There you go. You can keep it. Thanks.
你有多少钱？
How much do you have?
别都给他
Don't give him all of that.
- 那可能不够      - 肯定够了
- It's not gonna be enough.      - It's enough.
- 就给我…      - 对不起，先生？
- Just give me the...      - It's enough. / Excuse me, sir?
嘿，我们就进去五分钟
Hey. We need 5 minutes.
- 五分钟      - 好吧！
- 5 minutes      - Yeah!
听着，这地方是成人场所
Listen, this is a place for grown-ups,
- 所以，你要守点儿规矩      - 闭嘴
- so behave yourself.      - Shut up.
这口气听起来倒像那么回事
That sounds about right.
- 再选一张      - 好！给我…
- Choose another.      - Yeah! Show me...
- 看仔细了      - 好的
- Concentrate.      - Yes.
- 红心王后      - 好的，看着，她在这儿
- Queen of hearts.      - Okay. Watch. It's already here.
再变一张…黑桃A
Show me... Ace of spades.
我想我知道咱们来这儿的原因了
Think I know why we're here.
技术不错啊
You've got good hands.
- 尼克！你好吗？      - 是的
- Nick! You alright?      - Yeah.
什么事儿？请坐
What's going on? Sit down.
- 伏特加马天尼？      - 谢谢
- Vodka martini?      - Thank you.
我也要一杯
I'll have one of those.
给她可乐
She'll have a Coke.
我妈妈如果想看到清晰的未来 她就得喝酒
My mom drinks when she wants to get really clear images.
是个人都知道
She's famous for it.
那给她来点儿含咖啡因的饮料
Maybe something without caffeine.
哦，等等
I've got it. Whoa.
给你五百
There's 5.
不用找了
Keep the change.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我还在组织里的时候
When I was in Division,
她母亲就是那儿最出色的先知
her mother was at the top of every watch list there was.
你曾经为组织工作？
You worked for Division?
你想了解组织？
You want to know about Division?
整整十年，没有感谢，没有报答
10 years. No thank you, no pension.
我就那么被抛弃在马路上 还被威胁再也不允许使用转换能力
I was put out on the street with a threat to not shift again.
我只在芝加哥 为妻子买礼物的时候用了一次
Only the sniffs caught up with me in Chicago.
当时却被嗅迹者抓住了
I was just trying to buy something nice for my wife.
第二天我就接到了一个电话 说她死了
Next day I get a call, she's dead.
车祸
Car accident.
可我妻子根本不会开车
But my wife doesn't drive.
那种感觉你也并不陌生，对吗？
But I don't have to remind you how that feels, right?
- 我们需要这个      - 一个橄榄？
- We need this.      - An olive?
那是个珠子
It's a bead.
我们指望靠它先组织一步找到一个人
It's supposed to lead us to someone we need to find before Division does.
请原谅，我可以吗？
Excuse me! May I?
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
是这样的吗？
Got it right?
比这个再圆点儿亮点儿
It's a little more round and shinier.
是这个
That's it.
这就是我看到的那样
That's just how I saw it.
它很快就会变回来
It won't last long.
我得把它带给艾米丽・胡 她是个被流放的嗅迹者
I'd take it Emily Hu. She's ex-pat sniff.
熟人介绍的活儿她才干 这是她的地址
Only works by referral. Here's her address.
谢谢，胡克
Thank you, Hook.
拜拜
Bye bye.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
这把梳子
That's her comb.
她是不是在外头有其他的男人？
Is she with another man?
是的
Yes
我看见一个男人和一艘船
I see a man... and a boat
她开不开心？
Is she happy?
会不会回到我身边？
Will she come back to me?
那可是艘很大的游艇
That was a very big yacht.
有什么可以帮你们吗？
May I help you?
胡克・沃特斯介绍我们来的
Hook Waters sent us.
一颗跟这个一样的珠子 可以指引我们找到一个女孩儿
A bead that looks like this one is supposed to lead us to a girl.
你们是组织的人？
You with Division?
你是在藐视我们吗？
Are you looking at us?
事实是，掉下这珠子的女孩
The truth is, the girl who dropped that bead...
应该带着个手提箱 它可以致组织于死地
is supposed to have a suitcase that will bring down Division.
卡西认为如果我们找不到那个箱子 我们就会死
Cassie here thinks that if we don't find it, we die.
那你相信她吗？
And you believe her?
她相当有说服力
She's pretty convincing.
好吧，可这说服不了我
Well, consider me unconvinced.
看起来咱们得稍等片刻了
Looks like we've just got to wait.
等什么？
For what?
再过一分钟你就会帮助我们
You have about one minute to help us.
这是这么？
And what's that?
那是你的…海报
That's your... poster.
- 这个珠子      - 这个是表
- That's the bead.      - That's the clock.
- 它…马上就…      - 你还有一分钟
- It's... right now...      - You've got about a minute.
你们不能把这东西当真
You guys can't be serious.
别看我
Don't look at me.
这女孩儿整天劲头十足的画图
This girl's been going at it with that plan all day.
可几乎这本子上面所有的事都应验了
Everything that ends up on this pad seems to be coming true.
我看着它就像在看一副照片
I just see it like I'm looking at a photograph.
瞧，我们也想把组织的人赶出香港
Look... we want Division out of Hong Kong...
跟你一样
just as much as you do.
如果你能帮我们找到这个女孩 事情就容易多了
It's going to be a whole lot easier if you help us find the girl.
你让我想起了一个
You remind me of someone...
我曾经认识的人
I used to know
好吧
Fine.
组织已经把这个发给全城的嗅迹者了
They've been spreading these all over the city.
你们可以在观塘码头找到她
You'll find who you're looking for on Kwun Tong Pier.
- 接着去哪里？      - 嗯？
- Where do you wanna go?      - Hmm?
打扰一下！
Excuse me!
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你们会说英语吗？
Speak any English?
- 不会      - 不会？
- No.      - No.
没关系，我只是想搭搭车
It doesn't really matter. I just need a ride.
咱们是老朋友，对吗？
We're old friends, right?
这么巧，好久不见了！
Didn't know you were here. Long time no see.
你漂亮了好多啊！你最近是不是去瘦身了？
You look great! Have you lost weight lately?
我知道，我应该打电话给你们的
I know, I know, I should have called.
上车
Hop in my car.
哇哦！哇哦！
Whoa, whoa!
基拉？
Kira?
真该死！
Damm it!
- 你在这儿干什么？      - 我的车走了！
- What the hell are you doing here?      - There goes my ride!
- 别      - 别，别什么？
- Don't.      - Don't. Don't what?
你就是那个全世界的人 都在找的女孩儿？
You're the girl everyone's looking for?
- 我会杀了你的，尼克      - 嘿！
- I should kill you, Nick.      - Hey!
你认识这个疯子？
You know this psycho?
- 你发生什么事了？      - 现在你想知道了？
- What happened to you?      - Now you want to know?
你什么意思？我以为你走了
What does that suppose to mean? I thought you left.
你一直不给我打电话
You stopped returning my calls.
组织的人把我抓走了 还把我关了起来
Division caught me and locked me up.
- 什么？      - 你居然都没来
- What?      - And you never came.
我在到处找你，真的！
I looked for you. I did!
你根本没找我
You didn't find me.
够了！咱们有要紧事做，别吵了
It's done! You had a thing. Get over it.
我真的建议咱们换个地方再聊
I really suggest we discuss this somewhere else.
走了，尼克
Let's go, Nick.
基拉，组织的人正在找你
Kira. Division's looking for you.
他们要找的是那个箱子
They're looking for the case.
你不也一样吗？
And so are you.
那箱子里装的是什么，基拉？
What's in that case, Kira?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只记得我醒来的时候是在一条船上
All I know is that I woke up on a boat
旁边有一个我曾写下的记录 说要找到你
next to a note I'd written saying to look for you
然后你会帮我找到那个箱子
and you'd help me find the case.
之前那几天的事我什么都不记得了
I don't remember anything about the last couple of days...
无论我多努力的想回忆
no matter how hard I try.
你肯定是被人把记忆删除了
You must have had yourself wiped.
这样组织会很难跟踪到你
Erased memories make it harder for Division to track you.
真可惜不是关于你的那部分
Not the ones of you.
我能跟你谈一下吗？
Can I talk to you for a sec?
能等等吗？
Can it wait?
我现在好像有点为难
I'm kind of in the middle of something.
不行
No.
你，我，还有我妈妈
You, me, and my mom.
之前我从没有预见过妈妈的死
I've never seen my mom's death before.
是她，尼克
It's her, Nick.
她能改变未来，让它越来越糟
She's changing the future, and she's making it worse.
- 咱们得甩了她      - 甩了她？
- We've got to dump her.      - Dump her?
卡西，咱们…
Cassie, we...
卡西！咱们才刚刚找到她
Cassie! We just found her.
可她并没有那个箱子
And she doesn't have the case.
就是咱们要找的那个
Which is what we're looking for,
- 如果你记得的话      - 当然！我知道
- if you remember.      - Yeah! I know.
咱们找到了她也就找到了箱子
We find her, we find the case.
- 是咱们三个人      - 对，然后也组织找到她
- The 3 of us.      - Yeah, and then Division finds her.
哦对，一下子找到咱们三个
Oh yeah, the 3 of us.
咱们躲起来他们就跟踪不到她了
We'll get a shadow so they can't trace her.
- 这样满意了吗？      - 不！
- Satisfied?      - No.
卡西，你要相信我
Cassie, you've got to trust me.
我不是来这儿跟你讨论诚信问题的
I'm not the one with the trust issues here.
你最好把事情快点解决了
You better do something quick
因为我画尸体已经画得恶心了
because I'm getting sick of drawing dead bodies.
就是他
That's him.
- 嘿！平基      - 嘿，尼克
- Hey, Pinky.      - Hey, Nick.
- 嘿      - 好吧，谁被人追踪？
- Hey.      - Alright, who's feeling the heat?
好吧
Alright.
事情是这样办
Here's how this works:
我会用10倍于平时的范围遮蔽麻烦小姐
I get 10 grand a day for shadowing Miss Trouble.
只要她一直在距离我20英尺的范围内
As long as she stays within 20 feet of me,
就没有嗅迹者能找到她
no sniff is gonna find her.
就算他们这会儿正拿着她的指甲
I don't care if they're standing right on top
站在咱们头顶上我都不怕
of us with a piece of her fingernail.
- 你高兴了？      - 算你赢
- Happy?      - Overcome.
那走吧，咱们找个地方再聊
Come on. Let's find a place to think.
平基，你妻子给你起的这个名字？
So Pinky, your wife give you that name?
不，是组织，亲爱的
No, the Division did, sweetheart.
过去的事了
Back in the day.
对不起，那个箱子的事儿 我真的一点儿也想不起来了
I'm sorry. I can't remember anything about the case.
郁闷
Shocking.
趁没死之前我能把自己洗洗干净吗？
Can I clean up without getting killed?
别忘了洗洗你的耳朵前面
Don't forget to wash behind your ears.
你有个不错的女友
Nice girlfriend you've got there.
是，她曾经是
Yeah. She used to be.
我遇到她时她正在康尼岛忽悠当地游客
I met her running cons on Coney Island tourists.
那个时候我们形影不离
We did everything together. Everything.
于是咱们也要形影不离的这儿坐着
So we're just gonna sit around
等她把她的钱拿回来
and wait for her to get her memory back...
然后指望着她能在卡维找到箱子之前 告诉咱们那东西放在哪儿？
and hope that she'll tell us where the case is before Carver gets it?
也许是“咱们”
Or us.
好计划
Great plan.
你去哪儿？
Where you going?
我看见楼下有一盘鸡肉？一起来吗？
I saw a chicken place downstairs. Want to come?
不，不去了，我想待在这儿 看看有没有什么能帮忙的
No, I'm good. I want to stay here, see if I can help.
那你随便吧
Have fun with that.
你去哪儿？
Where you going?
放松点儿，罗密欧
Relax, Romeo.
只要在这栋楼里，她就在不会有危险
I can shade her just fine out in the hall.
不需要变成一个先知我就能肯定这点
I don't need to be a watcher to see where this is going.
哦！对不起
Oh! Sorry about that.
我以为洗手间里着火了
I thought the bathroom was on fire.
我总得想个什么办法让你进来吧
I had to get you to come in somehow.
你控制了我？
Did you push me?
你不喜欢吗？
You didn't like it?
那就还回来
Push back.
我父亲希望我能找到那个箱子
My father expects me to find that suitcase.
我母亲也一样
So does my mother.
可是你并不能看清楚它，不是吗？
But you don't see it clearly, do you?
太多事情都在不停变化
Too many things keep changing.
我已经看到了你会如何死去
I already saw how you die.
你看到了吗？
Did you see it yet?
你知道，你其实可以改变它
You can change it, you know.
飞离香港的飞机每天都有很多班
Plenty of planes leaving Hong Kong every day.
哦，我们正在改变
Oh, we are going to change it.
你们把这个女孩儿罩起来了
You put a shadow on the girl.
可你知道这只是暂时的
You know that's only temporary.
那个女孩儿会让你那些小幻想化为空虚有
That girl is the one who brings all your little fantasies crashing down.
所以小姑娘，去告诉尼克
So tell Nick something for me, little girl.
告诉他我们马上就会让他的脑袋 像番茄一样开花
Tell him my family is going to make his brain pop like a tomato.
告诉他这就是我看到的他的未来
Tell him that's the future I see.
哦，兄弟
Oh, boy.
嗨！
Hello?
你在这儿啊
There you are.
那个会把咱们全害死的小鸡头在哪儿呢？
Where is the chicky-chicky who gets us all killed?
你喝醉了？
Are you drunk?
是
Yeah.
对不起，我不知道该怎么让这个烂醉的10岁女孩镇静下来
I'm sorry. I didn't know the procedure for stopping a blitzed 10-year-old.
我13岁了！ 我能为自己的行为负责！
I'm 13! And I am powering my use!
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
我这是在工作
I am working.
- 你，你会把一切弄砸的！      - 好了好了
- You screw it all up!      - Alright...
把这给我，这是什么东西？ 咱们先说说这个，卡西
Give me this. What is this? We talked about this, Cassie.
没有人会出事儿的
Nobody is going anywhere.
- 这是什么东西？      - 你不了解，尼克
- What is this?      - You don't get it, Nick.
可以说，她就是那个会把咱们都杀死的人
She is the one that kills us all, basically.
那我想咱们已经死了
Then I guess we're all gonna get killed.
对，一团糟
Yeah. Screwed up.
“咱们”，你不是在说…
By "we", you mean not...
也包括你
You, too.
棒棒糖女孩是个比我厉害的先知
Pop Girl's a better watcher than I am.
哇哦！没人说过还有先知的事儿啊
Whoa! No one said anything about a watcher.
我的能力只对嗅迹者管事儿
I can only work long-term against the sniffs.
- 很好      - 不！我是说真的
- Good.      - No! True story.
你们如果被一个先知盯上 被发现只是早晚的事
You've got a watcher after you. It's just a matter of time.
那咱们分头行动
Then we'll split up.
分散她的注意力总好过让她专心致志
We'll give her 2 things to track instead of one.
- 平基，你带基拉找个安全的地方      - 我不和他走
- Pinky, take Kira somewhere safe      - I'm not going with him.
无意冒犯
No offense.
我也不想带你，女人
None taken, cupcake.
我知道你爱这家伙
I know you're sweet on the champ.
我会去找你的
I'll find you.
让她睡会儿吧
Let's let her sleep for a bit.
她居然比我们小妹还要快一步
She's one step ahead of our sister.
父亲一定会很生气的
Pa pa would be very angry.
她看到我来了
She saw me coming.
我想是你低估她了
I think you underestimated her.
她早晚得死！
She still dies!
她走了，你知道
She's gone, you know.
我只是说…
I'm just saying...
- 你还好吗？      - 不
- You okay?      - No...
除非咱们找到那个箱子
Not until we find that case.
你最后一次看到它是什么时候？
When was the last time you saw it?
前天
Not since yesterday.
尽管我这两天已经努力了
Not for lack of trying, though.
如果咱们再不快点找到它 组织就会杀了我妈妈
If we don't find it soon, they're gonna kill my mom.
而这将会是我的错
And it's gonna be my fault.
看着我
Look at me.
嘿！看着我
Hey! Look at me.
你真的认为我会让这种事儿发生吗？
You really think I'm gonna let that happen?
你说过未来实在不停变化的，对吗？
You said the future's always changing, right?
只要能了解就能改变？
It can change just by knowing it?
未来可以改变 可并不意味就一定会改变
It can change. It doesn't mean it will.
- 这样就不错了      - 你要干嘛？
- Good enough.      - What are you doing?
你到底打算干嘛？
What are you gonna go do?
我打算努力一把让未来好一点儿
I'm gonna try and make a better one.
去找卡维是改变不了任何事情的
Going after Carver doesn't change anything.
我不会得救，你不会得救
It doesn't save me, it doesn't save you,
她也不会得救
it doesn't save her.
这只是时间问题，卡西
It's just a matter of time, Cassie.
如果我不去找他，他就会来找咱们
If I don't go to him, he'll come for us.
艾米丽，这是尼克
Emily, it's Nick.
听着，组织派了个支配者来香港叫卡维
Listen, Division sent a pusher named Carver to Hong Kong.
我需要你帮我找到他
I need you to find him.
就用他们给你的那个珠子
Just use that bead they gave you.
他肯定亲手拿过那东西
I'm sure his hands were all over it.
- 我们还没开门呢      - 我不是来吃饭的
- We're not open yet.      - I'm not hungry.
亨利・卡维
Henry Carver.
这张脸我有段日子没见过了
Now there's a face I haven't seen in a long time.
请坐
Sit down.
这家店的食物味道很不错
The food is actually pretty good here.
给我个好理由让我别杀你你
Give me one good reason not to kill you right now.
不错
Good.
打算支配我的大脑了？
Gonna try and get inside my head?
那就试试
Go ahead.
看看在我扣动扳机之前你能不能做到
See if you can push me before I pull the trigger.
哇哦！真是十年磨一剑啊
Wow! 10 years is a long time to hold a grudge.
我父亲可不这么认为
My father would disagree.
- 你真是个杂种      - 我曾经很崇拜你父亲
- You piece of shit.      - Your father I had respect for.
他始终捍卫着正义
He took a stand with great integrity,
比我见过的任何人都正派
which is more than anyone can say about you.
- 如果你想…      - 你以为我没有预见到现在的事吗？
- If this is your attempt at...      - Think I don't know this future?
啊？
Huh?
我掌控着这世界上最顶级的20个先知
I've got 20 of the best watchers in the world...
现在所发生的一切早已尽收眼底
tracking every moment of this time right now.
你会死的，尼克
You die, Nick.
你们都要死
You all die.
可你知道谁会活下来吗？
You know who doesn't?
- 我      - 你确定吗？
- Me.      - You sure about that?
好吧
Okay.
基拉是我们的头号实验品
Kira is our patient zero.
我们要利用她制造出一个
And with her we're going to create an army the world's
- 前所未有的军团      - 抱歉，我需要关心这个吗？
- never seen before...      - I'm sorry. Am I supposed to care?
果然，去他妈的爱国主义
Fine. Fuck patriotism.
如果不接受特殊的药物注射 这女孩就死定了
The girl will die unless she receives the necessary injections.
可你们如果我没有我，就休想找到它
And you're not going to find it anywhere but with me.
这可能才是你最关心的吧
Maybe you care about that.
告诉我，尼克
Tell me something, Nick.
她的血液是不是开始发黑了？
Her blood turn black yet?
没有？是不是开始流血了？
No? Insides running out?
还是她有意瞒着你这些事？
Or is she keeping that away from you, too?
我想你是默认了
I'll take that as a yes.
你应该已经知道事情的结局了
You already know the ending to this story.
无论走哪条路都必死无疑
You can only draw it so many ways.
我们会改变结局的
We're going to change it.
其实你自己也不相信，对不对？
You don't believe that, do you?
求你
Please...
别逼着我做伤害自己的事
don't make me do anything to myself.
杀了你就可以改变未来
Hurting you would change the future.
而我很好奇未来到底会怎么发展
And I like how this future goes.
那你干嘛要杀了他？
So will killing him.
维克多！
Victor!
我想是我刚刚救了你的命
I think I just saved your life.
不用谢我 从现在起你只要乖乖听话就行了
There's no need to thank me. You should just start listening to me.
你可真逊
You look like shit.
- 她在哪儿？      - 5A
- Where is she?      - 5-A.
- 她安全吗？      - 是的
- Is she safe?      - Yeah.
可是她病了，很严重
She's sick, though. Pretty bad.
我有个问题要问你
I need to ask you a question.
那箱子里装的是什么？
What's in the case?
一种针剂
It's a drug.
一种能激发异能的特殊类固醇
Some sort of psychic steroid that boosts our abilities...
但却会致我们于死地
but kills us.
他们想让我回去
They want me back
是因为我是唯一一个... 在实验中活下来的人
because I'm the only one... who survived the injection.
告诉我为什么这幅画上我会拿着她的一只鞋
Tell me why I just drew a picture of me holding her shoe.
她没事儿吧？
Is she okay?
什么？不！ 你们这么做太荒唐了！
What? No. You've got to be kidding me.
- 她快死了      -你们不能把我牵扯进来
- She's dying.      - You are not bringing me into this.
你已经被牵扯进来了
You're already in it.
我们需要知道这把钥匙是干什么用的
We need to know what this key unlocks.
拜托
Please.
卡西，那群中国人对咱们知道多少？
Cassie, how much do the Chinese know?
不论咱们做什么他们都了如指掌
Whatever we do. It could be more.
他们的先知比我出色
Their watcher is better than me.
我们只知道有个箱子 里面装着组织的试剂
We know there's a suitcase with a Division drug in it.
基拉把它藏在香港的某个地方了
Kira hid it somewhere in Hong Kong.
你能把找到它的方法画出来吗？
Can you draw us a way out of this?
如果摆脱不了那个贱人 咱们做什么都是徒劳
We can't change anything with that bitch tracking us.
咱们要做什么她都了如指掌
The second we do, she's gonna see it.
- 你这是什么意思？      - 她能看见咱们的意识
- What do you mean?      - She sees intentions.
不管咱们做什么决定
What we decide to do.
就是说，如果我决定过马路 她就能看到我穿越马路
I decide to cross the street, so she sees me crossing the street.
那如果咱们不用意识做决定呢？
What if nothing we did made sense?
或者不停地改变思路
Or we just kept changing our mind,
连咱们自己都不确定要做什么呢？
we didn't know exactly what we were gonna do?
能摆脱她吗？
Would that throw her off?
有可能，但咱们最终的目的 还是要找到箱子
It might, but we still have to find the case.
这把钥匙能打开的那个东西被遮蔽起来了
Whatever this key unlocks is being shadowed.
我看不见它
Like I've never seen before.
到这儿来
It's this way.
希望越来越渺茫了
That really narrows it down.
被遮蔽的物体我是画不出来的
If it's shadowed, I won't be able to draw.
有一部分楼层楼消失了
There's a building missing.
我想布影人想逃过
I thought shadows weren't supposed
像卡西这样的先知是白费功夫
to be effective against watchers like Cassie.
当然不能
They're not.
而且我们也没能力遮蔽整幢建筑物
We're not supposed to be able to shade entire buildings either.
你想见我？
You wanted to see me?
我需要你的帮助
I'm going to need your help.
所有的先知都能追踪到咱们
Watchers from everywhere are tracking us.
卡维，那群中国人
Carver... the Chinese...
所有咱们想做的事他们都知道
Anything we think we're gonna do, they know about it.
这就是为什么卡西本子里的咱们 怎么着都要死的原因
That's why we all keep dying in Cassie's book.
- 什么？      - 你会死在一个电梯口
- Pardon?      - You die outside an elevator.
噢
Oh.
那咱们怎么做才能改变这种结局？
How are we gonna make the future unpredictable?
只能是连咱们自己都不知道下一步要做什么
By not knowing what we're gonna do
直到要真正做的前一刻
until right before we do it.
- 就像一个计划没有打算      - 是的，对
- Like a plan without planning.      - Yes. Right.
好吧！
Okay!
我现在为每个人写下一个特殊指令
I'll write letters to each of you giving you specific instruction.
在我让你们打开之前不要看它
You don't open them until I tell you.
最后的指令，是给我自己的
Then the last letter, I write to myself...
然后我会把关于这些指令的记忆消除
and wipe the memory of ever having written them.
所以我要你找到擦除基拉记忆的那个人
That's why I need you to find the guy that wiped Kira.
- 没问题      - 听起来是个好计划
- Sure thing.      - That sounds like a great plan.
- 你还有更好的吗？      - 我们这是摸石头过河
- Do you have a better one?      - We're flying blind.
是的
Yeah.
卡西
Cassie...
我需要你再画一幅画
I need one more drawing out of you.
我要知道那个箱子的颜色和形状
I need to know the exact size and shape of that case.
还有里面的注射器的细节
And that syringe.
我们的先知说它就在香港
Our watcher said that the package is here now.
父亲
Pa pa,
我知道组织要找的是什么了
I know what Division is looking for.
是一支注射器
It's a syringe.
有这些药，我们会比组织的人更强大
With this drug we'll be more powerful than Division.
如果不接受特殊的药物注射 这女孩就死定了
The girl will die unless she receives the necessary injections.
而你们如果我没有我，就休想找到它
You're not going to find the stuff anywhere but with me.
你会死的，尼克
You die, Nick.
你们都要死
You all die.
你需要卡维的药
You need the medicine that Carver has.
我不会眼睁睁看你死的
I'm not gonna watch you die.
为了你我会回来
I'll come back for you.
我发誓
I promise.
我什么时候打开它？
When do I open it?
当你开始怀疑现实的时候
When you start to doubt the truth.
- 你们知道什么时候该打开      - 你确定要这么干吗？
- You know when to open these.      - You sure this is right?
不
No.
尼克
Nick?
带把伞
Take an umbrella.
快下雨了
It's gonna rain.
你也要保重
You be careful, too.
你差不多快让我们追了半个地球了
You make us chase you halfway across the world...
怎么现在肯让平基・斯坦 带你自投罗网了？
then you let a hack like Pinky Stein bring you in?
- 我病了      - 你病了？
- I'm sick.      - You're sick?
你根本不知道自己的处境
You don't know what you are.
维克多，给他钱
Victor, pay the man.
当然
Of course.
我当然知道我拿不到钱
I knew I wouldn't get paid yet.
等在这儿
Wait here.
你被跟踪了吗？
Were you followed?
我永远不会被跟踪
I'm never followed.
那家伙在哪儿？
Where is this guy?
- 哪艘船？      - 那艘黄的
- Which one?      - The yellow one.
- 大的那个？      - 对
- The big one?      - Yep.
吴常？
Wo Chiang?
你是为了那个女孩儿来找我的？
You are here about the girl?
你就是那个把基拉记忆消除的人？
You're the one that wiped Kira?
12年前，有跟女人告诉我 会有个美国女孩来找我
12 years ago, a woman told me an American girl would come.
两天前，基拉来了
That was 2 days ago, Kira showed.
我想你帮我做件事
I have a job for you.
两个小时前，我写了七句话
2 hours ago, I wrote 7 letters.
我需要你帮我把这段记忆删了
I need you to erase the memory of ever having written them.
七句话和两个小时中的记忆
7 letters, 2 hours of memory.
那个女人也跟我说了这些事
The woman tell me those things.
她也没给你报酬吧
She did not pay for you, too.
等你做完了 我要你打开这个读里面的内容
And when you're done, I need you to open this and read it.
七点三十四分
7:34pm
- 再给我一分钟      - 随你
- I need a minute.      - As you wish.
我不会醒来后连自己都不认识了吧？
I'm not gonna wake up and forget who I am, am I?
等等等等，不，算了，继续
Wait, wait. No, just... go.
全没了
It's all gone.
未来，看不见了
The future has... disappeared.
我失去了线索
I lost the connection.
站住，请出示证件
Sir, your credential, please.
我是警察
I'm here for inspection.
告诉我安全储物柜在哪儿
I want to know where the lockers are.
哦，先生，在楼顶
The top floor, sir.
你到上面就能找到了
You can find them up there.
- 从这里上去？      - 是的
- Up this way?      - Yes.
一切顺利
No problem.
您的使命完成了
The job is over.
不需要再遮蔽这幢大楼了
You don't have to shadow the building anymore.
是那女孩儿派我来的
The girl sent me...
谢谢
Thank you.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
一样的尺寸，一样的颜色
Right size, right shape.
没问题
No problem.
你最好快点儿，持续不了太久的
Better hurry. Won't last long.
“藏起来”
"HIDE"
真扯
Crap.
“回家”
" Go Home "
自投罗网
The Lord giveth.
你认为你真的可以带着这个箱子顺利溜了吗？
Did you really think you could slip out of town with this?
告诉我，这东西真值得你为之丧命吗？
Tell me, was this worth dying for?
别，他会慢慢死去的
No. He dies slowly.
你妹妹答应事成后会给我一笔报酬的
Your sister promised me that and a great deal of money.
你知道世界上多少人会为了这个药剂厮杀吗？
Do you know how many people in the world would kill for this drug?
那么现在告诉我
Now...
卡西在哪儿？
Where is Cassie?
让我的后背复原
Get me back on my feet.
你们好像不是那么靠得住
You don't seem to be reliable.
你没想到是这样，对吧？
Didn't see that one coming, did you?
你真的想跟我玩儿吗，小姑娘？
Do you really want to do this, little girl?
我知道药在哪儿
I know where the drug is.
更重要的是，我知道你会怎么死
More importantly, I know how you die.
你想知道老虎意味着什么吗？
Do you want to know what the tiger means?
那药剂就在这儿
The drug is here.
看看这能不能帮你取悦父亲吧
See if that will make him love you.
我的画上说我应该告诉你
My note says I'm supposed to tell you...
基拉被组织控制了，在八塘街216号
the Division has Kira. 216 Batang Street.
听说那有很多他们的爪牙 是不是每个人都很难对付？
It said a lot on there. Was everyone's that complicated?
我相信你能搞定
I knew you could handle it.
这个免疫抑制剂不但能救你的命
This immuno-suppressant will save your life
还会让你完全康复
and allow you to reach your full potential.
你会变得比现在强大，基拉
You're going to be a better you, Kira.
你必须接受这个事实
You need to accept this reality.
我们并没有打算伤害你，基拉
We're not trying to hurt you. Kira.
事实上，你对我们而言相当重要
Matter of fact, your well being means everything to us.
我们理解，你忘了自己的身份
Understand it's not your fault you're forgetting
并选择逃跑并不是你的错
who you are and running from us.
那药物有副作用
The drug has side effects.
而我们并不知道这副作用的危害性
We have no way of knowing the severity.
我希望你知道为此我很自责 郝丽斯长官
I want you to know that I blame myself for that, Agent Hollis.
这不是真的
This isn't real.
你是自愿的，基拉
You volunteered, Kira.
我曾经反对过
I was against it.
可你坚信你能从药物试验中活下来
You were certain you'd be the one to survive the drug.
因此我不得不支持你 毕竟，咱们曾经是搭档
I had to support you. After all, we were partners.
可是你跑了
Then you panicked.
你真的认为你能逍遥自在
Did you think you made it all the way here...
的逃离我们这么久吗？
and eluded us for so long without any training?
你一直都在组织的视线范围内，基拉
That's the Division in you. Kira.
让我帮你回忆起来
Now let me help you remember.
Let me help you remember.
我一直努力想画些其它的东西出来 可我不行
I keep trying to draw something different, but I can't.
无论我画什么似乎都和我的死有关
It's something to do with how I die.
这不过是个老虎罢了
It's a tiger.
我是说真的
I'm serious.
我不知道我是怎么知道的 可我就是知道
I don't know how I know, but I just know.
我知道尽管平时我表现得很无所谓
I know I act like I don't care sometimes,
- 可我真的不想死      - 卡西
- but I don't want to die.      - Cassie...
你不会死的，好吗？
It's not gonna happen, okay?
告诉我我是个蹩脚画家 我画的都不会成真
Just tell me that I'm a crappy artist and that I'm wrong.
你是个蹩脚画家 你画的都是假的
You are a crappy artist and you are wrong.
听我说
Listen to me.
你已经做了比别人多很多的事情
You've already done more than enough for everyone.
现在你唯一需要考虑的
The only thing you've got to worry about right now
- 就是保护自己的安全      - 可我该怎么做？
- is keeping yourself safe.      - But how?
开始走
Just start walking.
想都不要想自己要往哪儿去
Don't even think about where you're going.
只管走，别做任何决定 以免其他先知能够追踪到你
Just keep moving. And don't make any decisions any watcher can track.
当你到达一个安全地带
And when you come across someplace safe,
就藏起来，就这么简单
you hide. Simple as that.
我不知道原因是什么 可我知道这么做一定管用
I don't know how, but I know this is gonna work out.
我发誓，别怕，相信我
I promise. No need to be scared. Trust me.
可爱多了
That's more like it.
你要干嘛去？
What are you gonna do?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
“湾仔街市”
" Wan Chi Market "
一杯奶茶 少糖
One cup of English tea, no sugar.
- 两碗云吞面      - 很便宜啊 大减价！
- 2 Wonton noodles.      - Very cheap. On sale!
- 美味云吞面     - 几好吃啊
- Wonton noodles. - It tastes pretty good. I'm so happy.
要不要
Food delivery.
“注册”
" Registrated "
你让我在我家人面前看起来像个白痴！
You make me look like a fool in front of my family!
别担心
Don't worry.
你什么都不会记得了
You won't remember a thing.
你母亲会为你感到骄傲的
Your mother's very proud.
我想跟你作笔交易 用药剂换那女孩儿
I want to make a deal. The drug for the girl.
没问题
Okay.
门源路，4号码头
Dock 4, Man Yuen Street.
尼克，箱子在哪儿？
Where is the case, Nick?
基拉！
Kira!
继续
Go ahead.
还记得咱们在过山车下的那夜吗？
Remember that night under the roller coaster?
我们任凭雨水打湿身体
We parked in the rain and got those little bottles of Jack.
那是你第一次说你爱我
That was the first time you told me you loved me.
他记得
He remembers.
我想亲口听他说
I want to hear it from him.
我记得
I remember.
那绝不可能发生
It never happened.
我昨天才第一次遇见你
We met for the first time yesterday.
你从没去过康尼岛
You've never been to Coney Island.
没有人去过康尼岛
Nobody's been to Coney Island.
我利用了你，尼克
I used you, Nick.
等一找到那个箱子 我就会让你忘掉这一切
And the quicker we find that case, the quicker I'll let you forget it.
你可以先接电话
You might as well.
我的卡片上说你必须要拿到注射器 把电话给卡维
My card says you have to take the drug. Give me Carver.
找你的
It's for you.
- 喂！      - 你想要箱子
- Hello!      - You want the case,
就得让他们活着
you let them live.
我会告诉你箱子在哪儿
I'll tell you exactly where it is.
- 再来一杯？      - 好啊
- Another?      - Sure.
壮行酒
One for the road.
不用这么难过
Don't feel too bad.
控制基拉的大脑比别人更有效
That push of Kira's has worked on better men.
4100号
杀了他
Kill him.
这么做你不介意吧？
If that's alright with you?
这个箱子
The case...
卡维长官
Agent Carver.
这箱子里装的东西
The contents of this case are the property
是属于美国政府的财产
of the United States government.
政府？在这儿我们就是政府
Government? We are the only government here.
放聪明点儿 没必要造成不必要的伤亡
Be reasonable. There is no need for anyone to die.
咱们很久没有交流了
We're not much for diplomacy these days.
维克多！掩护我们！
Victor! Make me a way out of here!
基拉！
Kira!
基拉
Kira...
哇哦！真令我惊讶
Whoa! I'm impressed.
工程师们总是对自己的工作尽职尽责
The engineers are always conservative with their projections...
可这次不是这么回事儿
but this is something else.
嘿！咱们是一伙的，忘了吗？
Hey! We are on the same side. Remember?
现在你何不叫这些人
Now why don't you march the men
把自己打发了，咱们就可以收工了
who tried to kill us off this roof, and we'll call it a day.
等等！基拉！不能那么做！
Wait! Kira! Don't do this!
你被控制了，卡维对你说的都是假的
It's a push. What Carver told you is a lie.
我承认那张卡片是组织伪造的
I'm sure they make a card for this.
咱们在哪儿？
Where were we?
你并不想这么做的
You don't want to do that.
看着我
Watch me.
如果你这么做你就算帮我的忙了
You'd be doing me a favor if you did.
那针管里的东西会杀了你的
What's in that needle will kill you.
基拉能活着是万里挑一的几率
I went through hundreds of potentials to find her.
她是我们唯一的幸存者
She's our survival.
看着我
Look at me.
你认识我
You know me.
我也认识你
I know you.
看着我
Look at me...
Look at me.
让他杀了自己
Let him do it.
真是可惜
What a waste.
我跟你说了让你带把伞
I told you to bring an umbrella.
我以为你是说马上就会下
Thought you said it was gonna rain.
我也告诉过你有时候会不太准
I also told you I get things wrong sometimes.
雨水没准能帮你把脑袋上的颜色冲掉
Maybe it will wash the crap out of your hair.
真正的箱子在哪儿？
So where's the real case?
在这儿
There it is.
你认为你母亲从什么时候起就开始 就开始筹划这件事了？
How long do you think your mother has been planning this?
在我出生以前
Since before I was born.
就是这东西，尼克
This is the key, Nick.
组织一直在尽全力
Division will do anything to keep
保护它不受威胁
this from getting into the wrong hands.
所以咱们可以通过这个来找到你的母亲？
So we trade your mom for the drug?
我正在找办法
I'm still working on that one.
嘿！我给自己注射的到底是什么东西？
Hey, what was it that I injected myself with?
九龙酱油
Nine Dragon Soy Sauce.
真恶心
That's gross.
基拉怎么样了？
What about Kira?
你是先知，该你告诉我
You're the watcher. You tell me.
不用担心，咱们很快就会看见麻烦小姐了
Don't worry. We'll see Miss Trouble soon enough.
我该什么时候打开它？
When do I open it?
当你开始怀疑现实的时候
When you start to doubt the truth.
把枪放到嘴里
Put your gun in your mouth.
开枪
Pull the trigger.
（字幕调整lwrest）